Where Every Fantasy Comes True
Deep in the Valley is a comedy, romance film directed by Christian Forte.
Best friends, Carl and Lester, find themselves magically transported into an
alternate universe straight out of a real-life adult movie.
Hilarity ensues as they embark upon a journey of adult-themed mayhem while
Carl ultimately finds true love in the most unlikely of places.
Lester, played by Chris Pratt.
Carl, played by Brendan Hines.
Rod Cannon, played by Scott Caan.
Bambi, played by Rachel Specter.
Autumn Bliss, played by Denise Richards.
Daphne, played by Kate Albrecht.
Deep in the Valley  (also known as American Hot Babes in the UK) is a 2009 romantic comedy film
written and directed by Christian Forte, son of 1950s and 1960s teen icon Fabian.
The tone is lighthearted and emotional.